Advertise your product or brand here
contact www.OpenSubtitles.org today
The lore tells us
of a valiant few
who stood above the fray
and fog.
My, what weapons
they must have wielded.
Which brings us
to our current exhibit,
the mythical staff
of the gods.
In Homer's tale,
the staff was said to harness
the gift of all gods.
Oh.
Welcome, proud soldiers.
What did I say?
Museums are fun.
Amusement parks
for the brains.
- Whoa!
- Okay,
there's no reason
to get pushy.
Everyone will get a chance
to see it.
Carved from a heartwood
not seen in over 2,000 years,
the two halves
of this ancient replica
were recently discovered in,
of all places,
a waste processing plant
outside of Philadelphia.
So strong,
they reportedly broke
three trash compactors.
Okay, um, friends,
that's enough.
I'm, I'm sort of the star
of the show here...
Stop!
Stop! Sir!
Sir!
Hey!
Hey, what are you doing?
Unleash the chaos.
Wait,
wait. Move, move, move!
No, no!
Help me!
No!
Ladies, please just let me go.
Oh, my God! Look out!
Turns out museums are fun.
Let's have more of it.
We can do nothing while
the staff remains sundered.
The champions of this realm
outnumber us.
Human champions
are still humans
and we are gods.
Do not underestimate
the judgement of the wizard.
To protect the power
of the gods,
he will have chosen
with meticulous precision
the strongest, most keenly
intelligent champions
this realm has ever witnessed.
I'm an idiot.
I don't deserve these powers,
if I'm being honest.
Like, what am I even
contributing?
There's already a superhero
with a red suit,
with a lightning bolt on it
and I'm fast, but he's faster.
Aquaman is literally huge,
and he's so manly
and Batman is so cool!
And I'm just me.
And I can't say this
to anyone else,
'cause my family looks to me
as a leader,
but I feel like
a fraud.
You understand I'm a...
pediatrician,
right?
I mean, yeah, well,
you were recommended
by another patient,
Billy Batson.
It doesn't matter.
Can you help fix my thoughts
so that
they just, like, you know,
stop happening?
All right, look.
And, again, pediatrician,
not a psychiatrist,
but it sounds to me like
you're experiencing
imposter syndrome.
And often, that originates
from trauma early in life,
so if you don't
mind me asking,
how well do you remember
your childhood?
Like it was today.
Trauma? Uh, I don't know.
I mean, I never met my dad.
Uh, my mom abandoned me
at a Christmas carnival.
I spent a lot of time
in the foster system,
ran away from 11 homes,
got into a lot of fights.
Then I was abducted
by a wizard
who gave me superpowers
and then dude just, like,
died in front of my face.
That's not a small amount.
A doctor conjured seven demons
and held my whole family
hostage,
so we had to rip out
one of his eyeballs,
and then everybody
got superpowers,
but now everyone's kind of,
like, doing their own thing
and I'm the only one trying
to keep everybody together.
Okay, okay.
Well, let's just process that.
Right?
Rejected by your parents,
then by the system,
and now rejected by a city
you try to protect.
I never said I was rejected
by my city.
"Rejected by city."
That's the Tribune.
Nobody reads the Tribune.
-I do.
-Anyway, okay, well, um...
I, uh, appreciate your help,
but I got some real problems.
There's this terrorist hostage
situation going on, so...
-Hostage situation?
-Yeah.
I suck balls at this.
Why do we always have
to play war games?
Hey, it's practice
for our other job.
I'm serious.
Military strategy,
multiple team members,
each with a special skillset
unleashed against
an unknown enemy.
I know how it sounds,
but the house keeps getting
struck by lightning, Leo.
I'm telling you.
Besides, you're the one
always talking about teamwork.
But we don't need guns!
Darla?
This is it.
This is big time.
- We are the guns.
- Darla!
Why were there Skittles
in my pockets?
It was supposed
to be a surprise.
It was.
Hmm, she's very moody lately.
Why do you think
I put Skittles in her pocket?
- Oh.
- Whoo! Ole.
Is this an army
of unicorns
-killing Genghis Khan?
-Yes.
Unicorns aren't real.
It's called speculative
history, Eugene. Look it up.
Billy,
you can't just leave.
Your guy's gonna die!
Whoo!
-See?
-Yes.
I told you
you would get into it
if you gave it a chance.
Yeah, I'm really starting
to see the appeal.
What's going on?
Dude, what are you doing?
Possible 10-99 in progress.
Multiple reports of cracking
on roadway.
Fraying suspension cables.
All units
to the Ben Franklin Bridge.
Yeah.
It's crazy music, Freddy.
It is, isn't it?
Very urgent melody to it.
We should see it
performed live.
I was thinking the same thing.
I feel like we can get tickets
to that concert.
Two. Maybe not six.
All or none. That's the rule.
Yet I'm still gonna
walk backwards now.
So, now's your last
and final chance.
Billy Batson, come with me.
No, no, no!
Man, it sure is a beautiful
day in Philadelphia!
Is it though?
-Almost finished.
-Again?
- Okay.
- This better be good.
Whoa, whoa!
Where's everyone going?
Um...
To fight crime?
-Okay.
-Bye, Mom.
-Bye.
-Bye, Rosa.
Give it time.
You guys ready?
Shazam!
Oh, my God.
It's gonna break!
Run!
♪ I need a hero ♪
♪ I'm holding out for a hero
Till the end of the night ♪
♪ He's... ♪
No, no, no.
No way, shut up!
Did I just save you
while you were listening
to this song?
No! I got you, I got you.
No need to panic.
Captain Everypower is here.
Oh.
I'm just kidding,
it's real easy.
Hi!
Oh, my gosh. Kittens!
Oh! They're so cute!
Did she just leave us?
Okay, let's go.
-Okay.
-No, no, no, I got ya!
That's my sidekick.
Captain Everypower Junior.
Hey! Junior?
You're gonna
wanna hold on tight.
Everyone's safe.
Awesome job, Mary.
Circle up, fam!
All right,
here's the situation.
We have one more job to do
and that's to keep this bridge
from collapsing.
The Ben Franklin
Bridge has collapsed.
Fortunately, there are
no casualties.
Thanks in part
to our local heroes,
one with me now.
It's great to be here, Nancy.
What can I say?
It's all in a day's work.
Right. Well, how do you feel
about being dubbed
the Philadelphia Fiascoes?
Given that that's not
an official title,
we feel nothing about it.
That is not our name.
Right, but
the important thing is...
What is wrong
with these people?
Have you ever no...
I'm gonna go check
on the kids.
Yeah, you should.
God only knows what they're up to.
Probably drugs, right?
Probably taking selfies
while vaping on TikTok.
Oh.
Is that a kitten?
No.
I'm gonna name you Tawny.
"Destroy bridge"?
What?
Not saving is different
than breaking. Am I wrong?
Am I wrong about this? Also,
we saved countless lives.
A hundred sixty-two.
It's countable.
Emotionally countless,
Mary.
Where's Eugene?
Where he always is.
Mapping out the Room of Doors.
Eugene!
Hey, buddy! Where you at?
Hey, Eugene.
Hello? We have a meeting,
Eugene.
Oh.
You're late.
Do not go in there.
All right, fam-jam,
let's jump in.
All right, big day,
big bridge,
kind of a couple blunders,
right?
But we're gonna meditate
on those mistakes right now.
Mary?
Organic chem is my meditation.
Said nobody with friends ever,
really.
In point of fact,
I'd have friends
if I had gone to college.
In point of fact
is exactly the kind of
smart thing
that a smart person
who doesn't need
to go to college says.
So,
let's go back to the tape.
Now, guys, as you can see,
we started off real, real,
real, real strong, right?
Right up top, all that
cohesiveness, energy,
terrific!
Oh, sorry, Coach.
Gotta fly IRL.
No, no, no, I'm not done
with the presentation.
I know. And I love
these daily recaps.
I just gotta spread my wings
a bit before dinner.
-It helps keep me loose!
-Okay, fine, fine. No recap.
We'll go have a group hang
in the air. That sounds great.
I gotta test this slime
for toxicity
'cause I'm starting to...
tingle.
Oh. The, uh, Phillies game
just came on
so I'm gonna go ahead
and, uh, watch baseball.
It's right that I give
Tawny back.
Oh, come on!
What is happening?
What is happening right now?
All or none, guys!
If you say you have to work...
I have to work.
Why do you even have a job?
Wonder Woman
doesn't have a job!
-Stop.
-No, seriously.
Do you think she wears
a ponytail and glasses
and, like, nobody
recognizes her
and she's, like, an accountant
or something?
Just stop.
You are holding on too tight.
Just 'cause Freddy wants
to fly solo for ten minutes
doesn't mean he's gonna
leave you like your mom.
Or me wanting to go to college
means I'm abandoning
the family.
Oh. Okay, cool,
it's about college again.
I totally get it.
Yeah.
Do you really
not see yourself?
You turn 18 in five months.
They're not gonna kick me out.
They didn't kick you out.
Victor and Rosa
are saints, yes,
but you're about to age out
of the foster system
just like I did.
Yeah, I get it.
I know how it works, okay?
Do you?
Victor and Rosa
can barely pay rent.
And the state no longer sends
checks to feed or house me
and soon there will be
no checks for you.
I don't care if Wonder Woman
has a job.
I want to contribute.
At some point, Billy, like
everyone on Earth,
we have to get a job or...
leave home.
Nothing lasts forever.
I mean, it's literally called
the Rock of Eternity.
So, clearly, some things
do last forever.
Leave me to die.
Oh, but we come bearing gifts.
Magic.
Impossible.
This realm was sealed off
from magic.
Yes. After you ripped it
from our father's very core.
From every god in this realm.
From me.
Do you not remember
what you took?
What my particular power was?
The power of elements.
No. I cast a barrier
to prevent your kind
from entering the human realm.
The only way that barrier
could be removed is if--
Someone broke this?
How did...
Where is the Champion?
It was your hands that forged
this staff for our father
and yours that will mend it.
I told you
I would die before I help you.
Now, say the word.
Never. Never!
Never say never.
Say the word.
Say the word. Say the word.
Shazam!
Now we get to have our fun.
Fun is for children, dear.
We are at war.
-Oh, my gosh.
-Oh, my goodness.
-I am so sorry!
-I'm so sorry!
No, don't be sorry. I'm sorry!
No, it's totally my fault.
Are you okay?
-I'm okay, yeah.
-Okay, yeah.
-I'm always okay.
-Good.
Uh, actually, do you...
do you know where this is?
Miss Saunders!
Yeah, absolutely
is what I meant to say.
Voice crack. It's weird.
Oh, no, no worries. If it
makes you feel any better
it's nothing compared
to the amount
that you're blushing
right now.
Oh, I blush
when I'm confident.
There she is.
-Hey.
-New girl. First period.
- Yeah.
- I'm Brett. This is Burke.
Listen, if you need anything
at all,
we're your guys. We got it.
Brett
and Burke Breyer.
They got it all. I mean,
what is it, narcissistic
personality disorder,
chlamydia, they got it.
Plenty of it
to go around, too.
This is Thundercrack's
Make-A-Wish kid.
Fanboy here thinks
he's a big boy now.
Yeah, he doesn't know
where he belongs.
Sure I do. I don't belong
in that trash can.
'Cause that's... I'll smell
like human garbage,
do you realize that?
And that's your brand, guys!
Down goes Freeman.
Hey, hey! Look!
-Now I'm a superhero.
-Nice!
What is this thing doing here?
Janitors.
Get up, man.
What are you doin'?
Come on.
You're gonna want
to get this fixed, huh?
Yeah, that's probably
why you fell.
- Yeah.
- Bye, new girl.
Jeez, thanks Mr. Geckle.
Don't sweat it. That trash can
was like a second home to me
when I went here.
Hey.
You knew those guys
were gonna hit you,
but you stepped in anyway.
You know something?
That's how I amuse myself.
The funnier I am,
the more
I get punched.
Well, it made me laugh.
So...
Hero.
You gonna walk me to class,
or what?
Why would I...
Walk you to class? No.
Why would I wanna do that?
Yes!
Thanks.
So, from the top.
What is Thundercrack's
Make-A-Wish kid?
Yeah. Um, it's real inside
baseball, but basically,
a while ago I happened
to have some lunch
in the cafeteria
with a few superheroes.
Wait, the kid who's friends
with superheroes.
-That was you?
-Yeah.
And they're still dicks
to you?
Sadly, just 'cause
you know someone cool,
doesn't really necessarily
make you cool.
You seem pretty cool to me.
Freddy!
Is my name.
Sorry, that was weird
and loud. I'm Freddy,
he said in a normal voice.
I'm Anne.
Anne.
-Nice!
-Bullseye.
Hey, you gotta fix
that crutch, bro!
What?
Good, little one.
Well done.
Now go find me the one
responsible for this.
Wow. Um...
I'm flattered
that you feel this way.
Truly, I mean, you know, like,
look at all this, you know...
Romantic setting
and fancy champagne,
big plates, tiny food.
I mean, you went all out.
I love that, I, I, I, I do.
I'm just not sure
that I'm really ready
to commit right now, you know.
Wait, wait, wait.
No, this isn't about you.
I promise this is
not about you. Okay?
Look...
I know the whole world wants
to see this happen.
You and me.
The dynamic duo.
The hottie goddies.
She-zam.
I guess I'm just afraid
that I'm...
gonna let 'em all down.
You know?
That I'm gonna let you down.
You know what?
Screw it. Let's try.
Let's try this crazy thing.
Maybe we'll, uh...
seal it with a kiss?
Billy Batson!
You are a fool of a champion.
What the hell...
What the hell is going on?
What happened
to her beautiful face?
Also, aren't you,
like, dead-ass dead?
I bring a warning
from beyond your realm.
The daughters of Atlas
are coming for you.
Daughters of Atlas?
They're coming to unmake
your world
and torture mankind
for all eternity
-in the Pit of Endless Agony.
-Okay, I feel like maybe
I should be writing
all this down.
-Quiet!
-Okay, okay.
You don't know
what you've done.
I regret ever choosing you.
Because of you,
the barrier between the world
has been brought down.
They will be hunting
for you now.
Hunting your family.
Hmm?
Oh, they're coming.
Listen to me, Billy.
The fate of your world
depends on it.
One thing you absolutely
must not allow
the daughters of Atlas
to do is...
Hey, Freddy?
Nope, over it.
Done it.
Check fraud? What,
are you kidding me?
Armored car heist?
I think I got that
in the bag.
Shazam!
Whoo!
Bon appetit.
Hi.
- Oh, hi! Yes, I mean, hi.
- Hi.
Um, you wanna show me
where you were sitting
when it happened?
Oh, yeah, of course. Totally.
-Yeah. Follow me.
-Okay, yeah.
So, basically,
it's a table down at the end.
So I was sitting, yeah...
Basically, I was sitting
right here, and he was sitting
right there.
- Here?
- Right there, yeah.
Oh, sorry.
Overbearing brother.
Oh, I have one of those.
Uh, a sister.
Always has to know where I am.
Right.
I feel that, clearly.
Always thinks she knows
better, too.
Even when it's been
factually proven otherwise?
Exactly. And it's not
that I don't love her.
No, of course. It'd just be
nice not to have someone--
Constantly breathing
down your neck.
-From the moment you wake up!
-'Cause I'm not a kid anymore.
No! I'm a month younger,
one month exactly.
And do we have to do
every single thing together?
No!
Oh! Billy! What...
What a coinkidink! Um...
I was just telling
my friend Anne
-what a great guy you are.
-We need to talk.
We need to talk.
This guy loves to talk.
-He's a great talker.
-Freddy.
-I have to talk to him.
I'll be right back.
-Okay.
Wait, didn't you tell us
the wizard disintegrated?
The skin peeled off his face.
He turned into a literal
pile of ash.
-Yeah, seems definitive.
-I dunno.
Yeah. Except now
he's in my dreams
and, Freddy, he's trying
to give me a message.
Could be
astral projection powers.
-What's that?
-Obi-Wan Kenobi-ing you
-from the great beyond?
-That's it, I'm calling
an emergency meeting
after school.
-I want you there.
-Where else am I gonna go?
-What?
-Dude.
Okay, first of all,
I didn't explode it!
All right? It was already
like that and, and, and...
What is that, the Tribune?
It's fake news!
Freddy, we only have one rule.
All or none.
And it's a stupid rule,
by the way.
I have a girl talking
to me, Billy.
A girl. For the first time
in my life!
And I probably don't have
a shot in hell with this girl,
but I'll never find out
if you keep trying to control
everything I wanna do!
Just be at the Rock, Freddy.
Okay. Mmm.
By the way, uh,
she has a sister.
Total control freak.
I think you guys
would get along.
Think you'd love her,
actually.
Look, look, look. Fam,
I know it sounds crazy.
And, and obviously
I don't know
exactly what this all means
but, but he was super aggro
and super loud and he was
trying to warn us, I think.
He was yelling about all this
wizard-y mumbo-jumbo
about realms and stuff.
Do you have to talk so loud?
Yeah, Mary, 'cause this is not
that loud.
I think this is
a perfectly acceptable
indoor voice volume.
What is the deal?
Are you okay?
-Yeah.
-Why do you have
sunglasses on?
Did you go to the eye doctor
this morning?
I dunno, it looks to me like
Mary did go to the eye doctor,
but it was last night,
and she had a lot of fun.
In point of fact,
I did have a great time.
I met other people my age
and I enjoyed myself.
You made friends
at the eye doctor?
No, she...
Yeah, can we get back
on track?
Listen, he's yelling at me
and he's saying the daughters
of Atlas
are coming to hunt us.
So, check out what I found.
"The daughters of Atlas
are the offspring
of the Titan Atlas..."
which is obvious,
but also Nyx, the Goddess
of Night and Death.
Well, good things
can happen at night.
And death.
Let me see this.
"The daughters
guard the mythic Tree of Life
which grows golden apples
that contain the seeds of life
which gave birth
to their realm
protected by a...
-dragon."
-Hey, now.
And I am suddenly here
for this.
I know, right?
'Cause, like, on one hand,
totally terrifying.
-On the other hand, dragon!
-Dragon!
Mary. What are we doin'?
I don't know, man.
This is your meeting.
Right, yes, fine, but we all
need to be on the same page
and, and, and look,
I often think that you think
better than me.
The wizard
did not exactly give me
a tutorial here, guys, okay?
Like, I don't know
how a lot of this stuff works.
That, that room of doors,
or that violin
that is, like,
constantly burning
which is super weird but also
definitely keeps
the lair cozy, right?
He didn't even tell me
my superhero name.
And it's not like
I'm not tryin'.
But I really,
really need your help.
Uh, I might know somebody
that can help.
Shut up. That lights up?
Shut up.
So, I'm mapping out
the entire lair
and you withhold this?
And you have really
been holding out on us.
Jeez Louise, dude.
- Whoa!
- "Whoa" what?
- Look!
Hey, Steve.
What?
You call the pen "Steve"?
Yeah, I thought he looked
like a "Steve."
He totally
looks like a "Steve."
-"'Crime and Punishment,'
a book report by Pedro Pena?"
-Yeah.
Pedro.
-Dude, that's cheating.
-I mean, he knows everything.
-Hmm.
-Seriously. Ask him.
You can just ask him stuff?
- Pretty much.
- Slick. Okay, cool.
Steve, we're looking
for information
about the daughters of Atlas.
Can you please help us
with that?
- These are book titles.
- Okay.
Let's just all pick a book,
or something.
Where's Freddy?
I mean, obscure mythology?
Definitely his thing.
I'm not even sure Freddy knows
what his thing is anymore.
You know I've actually never,
never been up here.
Don't lie.
This is where you hang out
with your superhero friends,
isn't it?
No, actually, why would
they ever have to...
Why would they ever come here?
I mean they have, yes,
they've driven by...
Do you actually know
those guys?
Or is this like
a "Canadian girlfriend"
situation?
Oh, you mean Collette?
Well, she and I
aren't really exclusive,
as of now.
Do you wanna meet one of them?
Meet, like how?
Like, face-to-face, right now.
I'm gonna take that as a yes.
And today is your lucky day,
because I'm gonna call
the hot one.
Her?
-No, the male hot one.
-Him?
What? Him?
Look, I mean, it's all
subjective, right? But, um...
Captain Everypower usually
tops most online polls
so... It's no big deal.
Is this a joke, Freddy?
'Cause I didn't mean
to make you
actually prove it, really.
No, it's not a joke.
And I'm gonna
call him right now.
I'm gonna call him right now.
So, don't move.
So, stay right there.
Hey, Captain Everypower.
What's goin' on?
It's your boy Freddy. Yeah.
Remember that time
I saved your life?
No, no, no, the other time.
Yeah.
Well, I'm calling in
that favor.
You must be Anne.
Oh, my God.
Friend of Freddy's, I hear.
I am, actually. Yeah.
How are you...
You know, I may be
the one with the superpowers,
but that kid,
he's the real hero.
Yeah. I mean, honestly,
I've never met anyone
like him.
He's... genuine
and warm and funny.
-That's a lot of nice things.
-Yeah.
How did you two meet?
Comic Con.
-What's Comic Con?
-What?
According to this,
gods considered
humans servants,
toys to be played with,
children to be punished.
Thanks, Steve.
Until the rebellion when
the humans turned on the gods.
I'm reading about that
right now.
So, apparently, all of this
revolves around
a powerful weapon.
So Atlas, uh, the father
of the daughters of Atlas,
obviously, yeah,
he crafted a quarterstaff
from the Tree of Life
and he used that staff to
give powers to certain deities
but also to take powers away
from others.
So, the staff's where Atlas
stored all supernatural power.
Yes, exactly. It's like a,
a battery for magic.
But when things got bad,
a council of human wizards
got together and they
stole the staff from Atlas.
And they used that to take
his powers away.
And once they had his magic
they went after other gods...
Guys, that's the wizard!
I know this guy,
this is the wizard
that I know!
What do these say?
"The Wisdom of Solomon,
Strength of Hercules,
Stamina of Atlas,
Power of Zeus,
Courage of Achilles,
Speed of Mercury." These are
the powers they stole.
No.
Whoa, guys, look!
This is what the name means.
Which is way cooler
than what I thought it was,
which is just a bunch
of hot garbage, so.
If I may point out one
of the powers
that may be possibly MIA.
Boop.
I'm sorry,
are you very unsubtly implying
that I somehow lack
the wisdom of
-Solo Man?
-Yeah.
Well, maybe it comes later.
I mean you do usually ask Mary
what to do.
-I'm just saying.
-Yeah.
This is very, very hurtful.
I just want you all
to know that.
And it's pronounced "Solomon."
Oh.
What else
have we learned, fam?
Well, once the staff contained
the powers of the gods,
the wizards apparently
encased the God Realm in some
magical sphere
sealing it away forever.
Cut off from magic.
Oh, so that's what
that was about.
Yeah, I don't think that
they are so cut off anymore.
A bizarre and gruesome scene
unfolded
in Athens, Greece
this morning.
Two women dressed in what
appears to be ancient Greek...
Whoa, whoa, whoa,
that's the wizard's staff.
How did they get that?
So, all those statues
used to be people.
I'm wondering, how did
the staff end up in Europe,
where Greece is at?
Oh, gee-whiz, mister,
sorry I took your cane.
You want it back?
I mean, I did break it in half
and then throw it away.
So, that's probably
where the journey started.
-You know?
-What?
What do you mean,
"What?" What?
-You just left it there?
-We were all there.
Guys, I had a staff.
I gave you all superpowers.
You're welcome, by the way.
And then I had to break it
in half so Sivana didn't do
super bad-guy stuff with it,
okay?
You broke the staff,
meaning you broke the barrier
between worlds.
Which we now know.
We also now know
what they look like,
so when they come to hunt us,
we'll see those two
-coming a--
-Three.
What?
Atlas had three daughters.
Kalypso, Hespera,
Anthea.
Anne... thea.
You know, I'm not
just a superhero.
I'm a super listener.
And...
I sense...
that you may have feelings
for Freddy.
Just wanna know
when he's coming back.
Don't want him to get hurt.
Oh, well, Anne...
I mean, we can't choose
the people we fall for.
What?
I'm not talking about that.
If he shows up now,
he's in serious danger.
Whoa! Look who you're with.
What could possibly
be dangerous?
Us.
Okay.
I see how it is.
Let's dance.
Oh, my God.
Freddy?
Ow!
Oh, Freddy, I, I didn't know.
I never meant
for you to get hurt.
Oh, I'm not the one
who's gonna get hurt.
Shazam!
Shazam.
- What's going on up here?
- Mis...
Freddy, are you all right?
Get back inside.
Just get back inside,
Mr. Geckle.
I'm okay. Go back inside.
Who are you?
Do you have kids here?
What are you doing?
Don't hurt him.
I won't touch him.
You have my word.
Mr. G. Wha...
What did she say?
What are you doing?
What are you...
no, no, no!
Stop, stop, stop! Wait,
wait, wait! Hey, no, no, no!
Wait, no, no, no!
I forgot how easily
they burst.
Why would you do that?
Like grapes.
What the... Huh?
Now, child, tell us where
to find the others.
No need.
Clip his wings, Anthea.
Ow.
Wait.
There are more.
-Perfect. We take them all.
-No.
That's not why we're here.
We're here for the seed
of life. Yield, sister.
We stick to the plan we have.
Father would never yield.
And Father is dead.
Now, you know your place,
sister.
Or I will show it to you.
We do this our way,
not theirs.
Make one move...
...and I will snap
this child's neck.
Oh, Freddy.
Billy, no!
Billy, stay back!
They're using the staff
to take our powers.
What? What?
Sorry!
I'm sorry,
I'm sorry, just,
just save yourself.
No, no, all or none.
We stick together.
And that you will
because you cannot leave.
Let's see how you like being
sealed off in a dying world.
No!
Freddy!
From
City Line Avenue in the north
to the western shore
of the Schuylkill River
to Cobbs Creek.
The unidentified barrier
appears
to be in the shape of a dome
with no one allowed
into the city or out
with some suggesting
this strange magical element
may be the doing, or undoing,
of the Philadelphia Fiascoes.
- Holy sh...
- Shh!
I'm trying to sleep.
It is the only escape
from the tortures here.
Okay. Bleak.
Wait a second.
Hagrid beard, Batman voice.
You're the wizard.
You're the wizard! Oh, my...
You're back! Billy told me
all about you.
Billy? You know Billy Batson?
Billy Batson. Yeah,
he's my best friend.
I'm... I'm Freddy Freeman,
Captain Everypower.
Well, used to be.
It's complicated now.
She... It's complicated.
That halfwit Billy
gave you the powers of Shazam?
Yeah, he did. And he said
that you turned into ash,
but, but didn't?
Once I gave him the power,
I could no longer remain
in my realm.
But death would have
been a luxury
compared to being trapped
in this cell
with the knowledge
of my failure, and with you.
Mostly with you.
A little more sarcastic
than Billy said,
but, hey, all good.
-Let's just get out of here.
-"Let's just get out of here."
Yeah, sure.
I sound nothing like that,
but okay.
Here's what we've got, um...
A cranky wizard
with a cynical streak
and a precocious young man
with an encyclopedic knowledge
regarding magical shit.
There is no way these sisters
are keeping us in here.
These prison bars,
they're probably enchanted!
-What spells do you know?
-Please, stop talking.
How about an arcane focus?
I don't even know
what that is.
Fine, then let's make
a potion.
Like a potion of, um, giant
strength or diminution.
Oh! Gaseous form!
Yeah! Maybe we could
float out of here like a fart.
I gave my powers to children
who squandered it.
We will die here, Freeby.
It's Freddy, by the way.
"Freeby"? Where do you even...
The sooner you accept it,
the easier it will be.
Is this a tooth?
There's a tooth in here!
Hmm.
"Power
of elements. Power of chaos.
Power of axis."
These are primordial forces.
I don't know how we fight
powers like this.
I tell you how we fight it.
With the wisdom of...
-Solomon.
-Exactly.
We, we set up a meeting.
Yeah, we tell 'em we want
to negotiate.
Offer up our powers
for Freddy.
But then we grab one of them
and that's what we really use
to trade!
But what if they steal
our powers?
No, they won't, 'cause we know
how they work now.
You know what I mean?
If they just point
that staff at us, we dodge.
Like dodgeball.
-Hmm.
-Dude, I suck at dodgeball.
Well, maybe Pedro sucks
at dodgeball,
but not Super Pedro.
No, Super Pedro also sucks
at dodgeball.
Fine. Listen, all I know
is that there's five of us
and three of them.
So I think we should
send them a little invitation.
Okay.
So, Steve says that this paper
is a stack
of magical parchment.
You write a message
on the magical paper
and say the name of the god
that you would like to talk to
and then the paper folds
into a...
Oh, my God, yes!
A paper bird.
And it flies to the god.
Well,
that's kinda cute.
Hey, what about demigods? Uh,
you know, like, Wonder Woman?
Do you think she's accepting
bird letters right now?
Did the pen just shrug?
Hey, Steve, do I just
dictate to...
I do. Okay, cool, wad that up.
All right.
Letter...
Letter, writing a letter.
No, no, no!
I was just talking out loud.
That's not a part
of the letter.
Wad that up, too.
Maybe if you try
-speaking from the heart.
-Hmm.
"Dear daughters of Atlas,
violence is not the answer."
Child,
I will spare your life
if you're honest with me.
Honesty.
Yeah, wow, very, um,
ironic subject choice.
The other Champions...
are they children
like yourself?
What even is a child?
I mean, I know I shave,
like, every week-ish.
Yes or no?
No. Your answer is no
because nobody's stupid enough
to grant primordial god-like
powers to a bunch of kids.
-Give us their names.
-The names of the Champions?
Um, well, there's
Brett Breyer,
and, uh, Burke Breyer.
Are you guys taking
this stuff in?
Writing this down? No?
They drive a Dodge Ram.
He's lying.
That's your superpower,
not mine.
And she thinks
you're a total control freak.
One of you.
Probably you.
Hold him.
Don't...
What's happening?
What is that?
What's she doing?
Power of chaos.
It enters a man's mind
and shatters it whole.
Oh.
My mind is already trash,
so I'd actually like
to see you try.
Because nobody has the balls
to handle what's
inside my brain.
Say their names.
Destiny's Child did it better.
He is stronger than he looks.
-Say their names.
-Stop!
Billy...
Billy Bats...
Billy B...
Stop.
This is from the Champions.
"Dear daughters of Atlas,
violence is not the answer.
Oh, good first sentence.
Thanks, Darla.
-We'd like to make a trade.
-What?
We'll give up our powers
if you give us Freddy,
add 'unharmed.'
Otherwise, they're gonna
monkey's-paw you.
Smart, Eugene.
Steve, add 'unharmed'
then, like, 'yours, trul...'
No, 'Sincerely, best'.
Maybe just signed
'The Champions.'
Should we proofread it?
Naw, Steve doesn't
make mistakes,
just writes what you say.
Great. I feel good
about this. Me, too.
Anyone else want a Gatorade?
Do we have red?"
What is this Gatorade?
-Is it a weapon?
-Sister.
We need not torture him
any longer.
You heard the letter.
- Throw them in the pit.
- Wait.
They want to make a trade.
And we will meet, sister.
But humans are not
to be trusted.
The pit is just a bad name
for a fun place, right?
Right?
Are you hurt?
No, just worthless.
-Well, you must get up.
-For what?
All this pretending
to be a superhero is just...
a way for me to pretend
I'm not broken.
Oh, feelings.
-I see something moving.
-Yeah, I see it, too.
Oh, shit.
What is that?
Ladon.
The guardian
of the Garden of Atlas.
-Run.
-I can't. I can't!
You're okay! You're okay.
I don't feel okay at all.
That's the power
of the dragon.
It emanates fear
from every pore of its body.
Ladon's fear paralyzes
any mortal,
so that none can approach
the garden it protects.
Power of axis. Very cool, very,
- very rare.
- Anthea!
I must go.
The door back to your world
is at the center
of the labyrinth.
Right, left, left
and then follow
the right-hand wall
to the center.
-You'll need this.
-How did you find this?
You once protected me
from the bullies
in your world, Freddy Freeman.
Now I've protected you
in mine.
Hero.
Well, to be fair, I didn't
actually need your protection.
I was about to rearrange
those boys'
internal organs
when you stepped in.
But you didn't know that,
which does make you brave.
I was just brave because
I knew I had powers.
No, the most powerful thing
about you is you.
How lovely
for both of you.
Goddess, we thank you much,
but we must get--
You should go. My sisters
don't need you anymore.
All they require now
is the seed.
-The seed?
-Yes.
Which remains hidden
in a place unreachable
by any of their kind.
Come, come, Jeff. Faster.
You call me Jeff?
She just said my entire name!
Hi, God... No?
Yo, Low Voltage.
When you fixing
this dome shit, man?
Oh, no, no, no,
don't worry, sir.
I have a plan.
-Really?
-Uh-huh.
'Cause look like all you got
is a sandwich.
No, these sandwiches?
No, these sandwiches
are important.
They're, they're
for a meeting.
Yeah, sure,
Colonel Cheesesteak.
Colonel?
Oh, boy, I really need a name.
Quiet one, she is.
I find it the most effective
way to slit an enemy's throat.
Is that...
Oh, you're totally serious.
Okay.
Uh...
Right, so, look, here's
the thing, um, you're upset.
A bunch of wizards came
and stole your powers,
which totally sucks balls,
I totally get it.
But, I kind of feel like
you're taking this all,
like, really personally
and, like, I don't even
know you, lady, right?
If thieves stormed your home
in the night
and stole all your coin
and then fled,
you would naturally
give chase, would you not?
And say, in this pursuit
the thieves
dropped the money
on the ground
and your neighbor picked it up
and kept it.
Now, imagine it is not money,
but the lifeblood
of your father.
The last breath
of your mother.
The power of all the gods,
the magic of the entire realm
that was stolen.
And now this magic courses
through you,
and you have the gall
to believe
that you deserve it?
This is very personal,
Billy.
You are very menacing.
I just want you to know that.
Like, I really...
I see the presence
that you have,
and that goes a long way.
But today, I really wanted
to talk about compromise.
There is no compromise.
I knew you were gonna
say that.
Wisdom of Saruman.
Don't mess with me, okay?
Give us back Freddy,
you take down this
sphere-y dome-y
magic bowl thing
and then, you know,
we won't have to annihilate
you into the ground.
It's a good offer.
I'm being serious.
You play the part of a man,
but you do not play it well.
Give us the powers, child.
All of them.
You are no leader, Billy.
You are a lost boy
who likes to make-believe
that he's a warrior.
Okay, look. I might not have
as much experience as you
'cause I'm not, like,
super old like you,
but I think I have
a few experiences
that you don't have.
'Cause I've seen all of the
Fast and the Furious movies,
lady.
And let me tell you something.
It's all about family!
Family!
Guys, that was the signal.
We practiced this,
like, 12 times. Thank you.
Forgot all about my family,
didn't you, Goddess?
No, human.
You forgot about mine.
Come on!
-Let's go.
-Pedro!
You're wasting my time, boy.
Yeah.
Whoo!
She sure didn't see
that coming
because she didn't go
to the eye doctor.
Uh, Darla,
that was, 'cause...
- A euphemism.
That was a euphemism.
No!
We've taken the power
from two
in your family already.
And now two more must die,
and for what?
So you can keep
playing soldier?
My father was Atlas.
Titan god of stamina
and strength.
His magic and power
may course through you,
but you will never
be a true god.
Oh, yeah? Did your dad
have superspeed?
Nope!
You okay? That was fun.
Let's go.
Come on. Come on, come on.
Hurry, everyone!
Let's go, let's go.
What?
You thought you were
just goin'
into some regular porta-potty,
didn't ya?
Which I can somehow
still smell.
Yeah, yeah, it really sticks
around. It's crazy, right?
-Yeah.
-Like, permeates
the air.
Doesn't matter. Anyway,
welcome to the Rock
of Eternity.
Only Champions
can get in here,
through any door that we want.
Little thing that we can do
that your sisters can't.
Guys, that's what I call
a total success.
Okay, maybe, like,
a partial total win.
- Told you I suck at dodgeball.
- Yeah,
you do, yeah, but you know,
look, Pedro, we all have
our weak spots.
You know what I mean?
And hers...
lack of strategic thinking.
Now for the real trade.
Freddy and the staff,
for your freedom.
And get rid
of the dome.
Oh, yeah.
And get rid of the dome.
'Cause the city
of brotherly love
is gettin' a little moist.
Word choice, man.
Yeah, I regretted it
as soon as
it was coming out of my mouth.
It's just
one of those words...
I know. I just...
"Dear daughters
of Asshat-Las."
Burn!
I just came up with that.
Make sure you put a dash
in there, though,
so it's really clear. Okay.
Man, it's so good having
Steve cover grammar
and spelling and stuff,
it makes me sound
so much smarter.
So...
"A brother for a sister, huh?
How's that feel?
Also, how are you
actually sisters,
because the age difference
is very noticeable,
and slightly upsetting,
I'm not gonna lie."
Even though I don't like you
very much,
I believe everyone
deserves human rights,
but you don't deserve
strawberry.
You only get yellow.
She's gone!
Wait, what?
I thought we brought her in
too easily.
She wanted to get caught.
I don't get it.
Where would she even go?
Well, this seemed inevitable.
Yep. We are so lost.
Thanks, bozo.
We are not lost.
Who's the wizard here?
I don't know.
You don't have any spells,
no magical artifacts,
you know nothing about magic,
you're just...
You're the wizard.
-Thank you.
-Whatever.
Now let's see if that
girlfriend of yours
can be trusted.
Get back, get back. Get back.
Okay, I think the coast is clear.
Let's go home.
One moment.
Did you not see
what she was holding?
It was an apple.
She wanted a snack.
What's the big deal?
The golden apple.
From the Tree of Life.
Oh, wait, hold up, didn't you
say that was somewhere safe?
-Billy!
-Billy. Gosh.
Where are you going now?
Nope.
She's not in there.
No, no, no.
That's a hard pass.
- That's a hard pass.
- Yo, Billy,
you don't gotta worry
about that one.
It's just a labyrinth
that doesn't go anywhere.
Like an ancient Greek
- labyrinth?
- Guys...
porta-potty.
Mmm.
Hespera.
It's over, sisters.
Now we can plant the seed
and restore our realm.
Or we plant it in their realm.
But that would destroy
their world.
Just as they destroyed ours.
You can't be serious.
- Yes.
- No.
No, that's not
what we agreed to.
Anthea,
you simpering bore.
She's right,
we've spent ages
waiting for this moment.
We have the seed.
We have the staff
and its powers.
We are not squandering it
for your personal
satisfaction.
No, I should go, not you.
Look, I know
what you're thinking.
The kid with the crutch
doesn't exactly
sing "sneak thief."
But here's the deal.
Your knees crack like crazy
when you walk.
It's pathetic.
See?
Fortune be with you, Freddy.
Thank you.
What did you just call me?
Freddy. Freddy Freeman.
That's it.
You nailed it.
I'll see you
on the other side.
Even if we did,
the Tree of Life
would not thrive
in their soil.
It would despoil, it would
disfigure into something...
Monstrous?
That is what humans are.
It is only fitting
that we bring
our monsters to their world
and do to them
as they did to us.
We agreed
to restore balance
and vengeance has
great measure of weight
on those scales.
Anthea, humans are villains,
even to themselves.
-No, not all.
-All.
Sister,
I fear your rage
has gotten the better of you.
Why?
Humans wreak havoc
and devastation,
then pray to the gods
to absolve them.
They actually pray
for order and peace
when all they do
is dismantle it at every turn.
Anthea, I want you
to take the apple
and plant it in our garden.
Of course
you turn to her.
Father would be ashamed
of both of you.
Where did that even come from?
-Hi!
-You favor her, Hespera,
and see how she betrays us.
Deliver him
to his proper fate, sister.
- No!
- Kill him!
What is that?
Great question.
No idea.
But made you look.
Billy!
-Oh!
-Oh.
Your crutch!
Oh! Shazam!
-Yes!
-No!
So, we have a lot
to talk about.
Kalypso, hand me the staff.
You are not fit to wield it.
More fit than you.
You had him in your hands,
yet did nothing.
Our sole purpose is
to avenge our father,
but everyone here
has become weak.
Ladon, world-eater,
rise from the pit!
Go, go, go!
Captain Everypower!
Where's he going?
What the...
Victor?
Victor, wake up.
Hello. Oh, God, woman. What?
Dad. We gotta go!
-We gotta get out of here.
-We have to go right now!
This is funny, right?
I know what this looks like.
That's not true. I have
no idea what this looks like.
Just don't freak out.
I said don't freak out!
Look at me, it's Billy.
Rosa, it's Billy, okay?
And that's Eugene,
-and that's Freddy...
-It's me.
That's Darla
and that's Mary, obvi,
and then Pedro,
just normal Pedro.
Guys, this is no time
for secrets, okay?
We have to tell 'em the truth.
- We're superheroes.
- I'm gay.
Yeah, we know, bud.
-You knew?
-Yeah.
-Oh.
-I'm the wizard.
-Oh, this is the wizard.
He's a wizard who's called
"the wizard."
Okay, get dressed right now.
Come on, hurry up.
Put on these clothes.
This is so weird.
Yep, yep.
You guys are
the Philly Fiascoes?
Okay. This is in no way
an acknowledgement
of that stupid nickname
but, yes, that would be us.
Now can you pick up the pace?
We have to go.
The dragon is here!
Dragon?
You okay?
Okay.
I know this is a lot
to take in,
but I promise
to explain it all later.
Explain what?
That our kids are superheroes
being hunted by Greek gods
that used a dragon to destroy
the house we just bought?
-Yeah.
-Wait, you bought the house?
Yeah.
Run! Go!
Oh, no.
Get down.
Okay, that's it!
Again?
Freddy!
Hey, hey!
This is what you want, right?
Come on, we're good.
We're safe right now.
Let's go. Let's go.
Mary!
No.
Hey. Are you okay?
You okay?
All right.
Now, where is this dragon?
Fitting place for a garden.
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Go! Let's go, let's go!
Oh, God, I'm slipping!
Slipping!
My shoe!
Holy moly.
You know, I never thought
I'd say this about a dragon,
but it is the least
of our problems right now.
Your world will not
survive this.
Yeah, no shit, Merlin!
He's right.
Anne!
-Are you okay? Are you hurt?
-I'm okay, I'm fine.
In the God Realm, this tree...
is a thing of beauty.
Of peace.
It was not meant
for the soil of this realm
and it's become monstrous
by the hand that planted it.
Whose side is she on, anyway?
Do you...
I must try to sway Hespera.
Only she can subdue
our sister.
I will give it my all,
or die trying.
Die? No, I'm pretty sure
we can come up
with an alternative to dying.
My sweet Freddy,
I'm ready if need be.
I've lived a long life.
What are you talking about,
"Lived a long life?"
We're the same age.
You're young. We're young.
I'm over 6,000 years old.
Oh?
You look great.
Oh.
Suddenly seems inappropriate.
Yeah.
We can't let her die.
She called me sweet!
We have to figure
something out.
Take my powers back.
-No, Billy!
-No, no, no.
Hey, take my powers back.
You gave 'em to me, so you can
take 'em back, right?
I am no longer the champion.
You are!
You think I know
how to fix this, dude,
but I really don't, okay?
I, I didn't even know
who those Greek sisters were.
I had to Google them.
But you know who they are,
which means you know
what to do.
And you were right.
You picked
the wrong champion, man.
I mean, that's why I always
say "all or none," right?
Because without my family,
I'm nothing.
And honestly, I have no idea
what I'm doin'.
No.
You don't have
a shred of wisdom
in that brain of yours.
But your heart is wise.
And it knows exactly
what must be done.
I spent millennia searching
for a worthy champion
and no one was worthy
of what I once shared
with my brothers and sisters.
But when you shared
your powers,
you did not hesitate.
For you, everyone
can be worthy
if given a chance.
Now, go fight for your family.
Go fight for the world.
I chose right
when I chose you.
Billy?
Billy, what are we gonna do,
man?
Same thing we
always do, Freddy.
Save the God darn world.
Now, I'm gonna go
get that staff
and I need you to lure
these things away
from the stadium while I deal
with the dragon, all right?
Wait, wait, wait,
Billy, Billy.
Can I just see you,
before you go?
Not this version.
You... You.
My Billy.
Shazam!
Is that why the house keeps
getting struck by lightning?
Hey.
I promise after this
if I don't get eaten
by a dragon,
I'm not gonna force you
to keep me.
-Okay?
-What?
I know I age out soon.
Billy.
My wonderful, kind,
brave, son.
You will never age out
of your home.
Never.
Now, do me a favor
and I mean this
from the bottom of my heart,
go kick their ass, okay?
I love you, Mom.
Me too.
Shazam!
That's gonna take
some getting used to.
Everybody to the battle wagon!
The battle wagon?
Trying to get
into the spirit of things.
Don't you see what
you're doing to these people?
I do.
And what I see is just.
Hespera, look at this tree.
It is blighted.
It is unnatural here.
We made a vow
to restore our realm,
not destroy another.
A god has answered
their prayers at last.
They did not know their place,
so I am showing it to them.
Your fanatical tone
echoes our uncle Hades.
No. I'm putting an end
to this.
Hespera.
No!
If your emotions rest
with the humans so, Anne,
then perhaps you should
be human.
Help, somebody!
Somebody help!
Okay, now what? There are only
so many minotaurs
I can run over with this van.
Hey, Steve.
What are monsters afraid of?
"The king of beasts."
Lions?
Unicorns.
Really? I love unicorns.
Yet, the unicorn
does not love you.
Guys, unicorns don't exist.
What?
- Oh, my...
- Ah!
I guess maybe
it's not so crazy.
The unicorn is the most
fearsome creature
of its realm.
Ruthless and cruel,
not like the ponies
from your storybooks.
They loathe humanity.
Is there anything
they do like?
"Dark caverns. Ambrosia"?
Ambrosia. It's like the nectar
of the gods.
It's supposed to be sweet,
like honey.
I have an idea.
Go, go! Quick, quick.
Guys, get as many of these
people to safety as you can.
Kids?
-Let's go.
-Come on, let's go!
Wizard?
I'm going with them.
Freddy?
Anne?
Anne!
I am not entirely sure
how to parent, here.
Hey! Khaleesi!
Whoo! That was
really satisfying.
How was that for you?
Yeah.
We love you, Thundercrack.
You're the best,
Captain Marvel.
-Yeah, go, High Voltage!
-Oh, wassup, bro?
It's Maximum Voltage actually,
amongst other names.
We're still kinda
workshopping it, so...
You thought you were
invulnerable.
But, no.
Magical fire.
Magic can kill magic.
Yeah, yeah, yeah,
"Magic kills magic."
Way ahead of you, lady.
I'm just trippin' out
because I've never seen
my suit burn like this.
Also, nobody messes
with my town!
Know what I'm saying?
I defeated
my traitor sister.
A god.
You think I won't destroy you?
The staff is absorbing it all.
Like a battery.
That's right.
Run!
This is a terrible idea.
You don't understand
the savagery, the barbarity.
Oh, no.
-Hello.
-No.
It's okay. Come here.
Darla...
It's okay. Good girl.
- Whoa, watch out!
- Whoa!
Darla!
Taste the rainbow.
Good, isn't it?
It's the closest to ambrosia
we have.
Good girl.
Whoa!
We're gonna need
more Skittles.
Taste the rainbow, motherfu...
No, no, no.
Lady, lady, you can't die!
Come on, Billy, come on!
Powers, powers, powers.
Medical powers. No.
How-to-fix-dead-people powers.
Clear?
Whoa! Come on!
One more time. Clear!
Stop! Stop!
Let me go to the Underworld
in peace, please.
Oh, lady, lady,
listen to me, okay?
I don't want anyone else
to die.
Not my family, not Anthea,
not anyone,
and we can save them.
This all came
from the tree, right?
I might know a way to destroy
the tree and the dragon
all in one.
Ladon's powers
are too great, boy.
Well, not if I can overload
the staff
-with enough lightning.
-A bomb?
Is that enough
to kill the dragon?
And more.
You would annihilate
everything that's inside
the dome.
Well, then I have
one more favor to ask.
Let's go, let's go.
Let's go.
There's shelter ahead.
Walk, don't run.
Let's go, let's go.
Keep going. Keep going!
Anne!
Go. Run.
Watch that rear.
Go, go, go!
Back away!
Run, run, run!
Anne!
Ladon,
kill the traitor.
Impossible.
Bow him!
I lost it. Freddy, I can't.
What is a god
without her power?
The most powerful thing
about you
is you.
You taught me that.
Kill them!
Boom!
That must be super
disappointing as a dragon.
Assuming that you are one.
I mean, you fly,
and you breathe fire,
but you're also made of wood
which is a weird flex
and a serious design flaw,
if I'm being honest.
Freddy, Anthea, don't!
Ah, made you look!
Oh, lady, that's twice.
And I didn't even need
a flaming violin that time.
You want the staff?
Come get it.
Now, Hespera.
Now. Now.
No.
No! No!
Remove the dome.
As long as I still breathe,
the dome still stands.
Till I see you
on the other side, sister.
Billy!
- Get out of there.
- I can't.
Billy.
I have to do this.
Billy,
what are you doing?
You're not supposed
to be in there.
Yeah, I am.
I used to think that
I couldn't do anything right,
that I didn't deserve
my powers,
but there's something
that I can do.
No.
I can save all of you.
But it's all or none!
Yeah.
All of my family gets to live
and none of them gets hurt.
Freddy, I've never
had a family. You know that.
Everybody I've ever cared
about, they all left me.
My mom, my dad, everyone.
So when I found you guys,
I had to hang on
and I've been hanging on
too tight.
No.
I should have let you
do your own thing.
Now it's time for you to fly.
What about you?
I'm Captain Everypower Junior.
Don't you forget it.
We end this now.
Yeah. We do.
Come on, Billy.
He's got this. We got this.
He's got this. He's got this.
Billy.
Fly.
Come on, baby.
Come on, let's go!
No!
Whoa!
Ah.
Shazam!
Billy.
A true god,
after all.
He did it.
We must go.
Billy?
Billy!
Billy. Where are you?
Billy?
Billy! Billy.
Billy!
Dude, wake up. You did it.
Okay. You're supposed
to wake up.
It's the part
where you wake up
and open your eyes and laugh
and you're supposed to say
you got me, 'cause you got me.
Dude. Joke's over, man.
Billy!
Billy. Billy, come on.
Freddy.
What did you do?
Wake up, Billy.
- Billy?
- He's over here!
Billy.
You asshole!
We're a team! We're a team!
Oh, Billy.
Billy.
Oh, my baby. No.
He was a hero.
He was a hero and a god.
And he should be laid
to rest like one.
Hey, pal.
Will this land ever come back?
The staff is drained of magic.
Only the spark of a god
can restore its power
and there are no gods left.
There is one.
What?
Whoa.
It's a zombie!
Guys!
What the hell?
You buried me?
In what, like, two minutes?
Oh, Billy!
Hey.
Oh, man. I missed you guys.
Hi. Hey.
Oh, my God. Hi.
Why didn't anybody tell...
Hi. Sorry, sorry,
I didn't, uh...
I didn't see you there,
I was, um, I was...
I was dead at the time.
So, you, uh...
you got my bird letter?
Oh, I, uh...
I think you've got
something...
On my...
Where... Oh.
What?
That's a spider.
I'm sorry, that's disgusting.
Also,
that's really embarrassing.
Yes, it is.
But it was an amazing thing
you did.
The sacrifice you made.
You brought this world
back to life.
Maybe this time,
gods and humans
can learn to live in peace.
Yeah.
Use the power of Zeus wisely.
Be well, Billy Batson.
Hey, you know, just because
your father's power
is surging through me,
that doesn't technically
make us related, you know,
and I'm gonna be 18
in, like, five months, so...
Stick to saving
the world, kid.
Yeah, you know, like,
that's... Okay, cool.
See ya.
What's with our boys
and older women?
Hey.
Who wants their powers back?
We can do that, right?
-Yeah.
-Yeah. Okay, good.
Good, good, good.
I'd like
our house back.
Can we do that?
- Dinner!
- Coming.
Aw. Thank you for respecting
the cross-stitch.
Anthea.
Have you decided what
you're gonna do
about that god realm of yours?
Well, actually I'm gonna take
some time off while it heals.
Spend some time
with the common folk.
Learn some about your world,
about how, maybe,
we can learn from each other.
Number one sign of wisdom:
Admitting there's always
more to learn.
I'm coming around to it.
I got it.
Whoa.
Uh, guys?
Guys!
It's the wizard.
- Oh, my God!
- No way!
-Yes.
-Look at this guy!
Look at him, he's so handsome.
You pimpin' now, what is this?
- You look amazing.
- You look great!
Well, I was
in the neighborhood
and, um, I just wanted
to express
my gratitude before I go.
Sorry. Doorbell's broken.
Actually, everything's broken.
Not everything.
You were just
in the neighborhood?
Okay,
I came for the staff.
Perhaps I will hold
onto it for now.
I also wanted to see
your faces one last time
before I turn into a pile
of ash.
-Wait, what?
-No!
I am making a joke.
I have an Uber waiting.
And besides...
...I've been trapped in rocks
and prisons for far too long.
It's time to see your world.
It's been an honor,
a privilege,
watching you all soar.
You know, you're not such
a bad wizard.
Thank you, Jeff.
It never ends.
Also,
what's my superhero name?
Your name is...
Shazam.
-Of course.
-Yeah.
I still think we can beat it.
My feet hurt.
How much further?
About ten seconds less
than the last time
you asked me.
I'm sorry, I just feel
like we could
have parked
a little bit closer.
He doesn't know we're coming,
and I didn't want
to spook him.
"Spook him."
He's a superhero, not a deer.
All right, let's go.
And then you can tell Waller
that even though
she thinks this guy could be
a good addition to the team,
we never actually met him
because you wore
shitty walking shoes.
Okay, first of all,
they're boots,
and they're not shitty,
they're new.
-I just haven't had a chance
to break them in yet.
-Shut up.
Waller said this guy
is as powerful as they come,
but a little immature.
Oh, great.
Whoo!
-Billy Batson.
-Yeah?
I mean, no.
I've never heard that name
in my life.
I don't know who
you're talking about.
But I'd like to meet
that person
'cause they sound super cool.
And funny.
And talented.
And ridiculously handsome,
but, like, in a dangerous way.
What the hell
are you talking about?
Relax. We know who you are.
-How?
-Don't worry about that.
Who are you guys?
Don't worry about that either.
Look, we've seen
what you can do.
And we're here
to make you an offer.
How would you like to join
-the Justice...
-Yes!
A thousand times yes!
Oh, my gosh!
I've been dreaming about this!
Well, I mean,
not this exactly.
Like, normally,
it's Wonder Woman
in the dream, but...
-Ew.
-Huh?
Well, that was easy.
Welcome
to the Justice Society.
Yeah! Aweso... Wait, what?
The Justice Society?
Is that different
than the Justice League?
Yes. The Justice Society
is different
than the Justice League
because of how words work.
I just want to be
in the Wonder Woman group.
-So, that's you guys, right?
-No.
Why are you so obsessed
with Wonder Woman, dude?
He's joking, right?
-No?
-Okay. I'm out.
I'm gonna wait here,
'cause of the shoes.
Can you drive by and get me?
Hey, just a little
constructive criticism.
It's pretty confusing
that there are
two separate groups
of superheroes
that are totally unaffiliated,
but both have "Justice"
in their name, you know.
Like, have you guys ever
thought about doing
a rebranding of sorts?
'Cause just a quick search
on Thesaurus.com,
you got so many options, man.
Like, "Authority Society." Eh?
Uh, uh, "Code Society."
That's stupid.
These are, like, legal terms.
"The Avenger Society."
I like that, for some reason.
Well, well,
Doctor. We meet again.
Where in the hell
have you been?
To implement
the perfect plan, Doctor,
one must have patience.
What are you talking about?
It's been two goddamn years!
Yes. But what is time
but a trick of the mind?
A meaningless measure.
Hey. I'm 57 years old.
I'm stuck in a concrete box
surrounded by lunatics
waiting for a worm to enact
some, what,
vague plan I've been told
absolutely nothing about?
It takes me a very long time
to get places, okay?
I do not have legs,
I do not have wings,
I just slither around
endlessly.
But not for long.
Tell me everything.
Just one more thing
I need to do.
What? No!
Oh, goddamn it!
Watch any video online with Open-SUBTITLES
Free Browser extension: osdb.link/ext